On June 9th, I really wanted to add, like, a juicy, nice little transit for everybody to look out for Venus.
Is that with this little mouth?
Yeah.
It's, like, sexy time, juicy day, okay?
Okay.
Because, honestly, we need to, like, dance and make out again, you know?
Because so many leftists are so depressed.
And I really miss making out.
I'm so good at it.
And I just, I like doing things I'm good at.
Like, I'm telling you, like, I don't even need to have sex.
I just want a good make out sesh.
We could just be second basing.
And I would be fine.
I still, like, remember the nightclub days where you would just, like, be dancing till 2 a.m.
and making out with a stranger.
I don't know if people do that anymore because of, like, COVID and the times are different.
I did that in Cuba.
It was a time.
Can I just tell a quick sidebar story?
Of course.
That I went, I walked into the club in Cuba.
And I spotted an individual.
And I turned to my homegirl, Kiki.
And I was like, that one.
And she was like, okay.
We were in the club for a good hour and a half.
And then he came up to me.
Ooh.
So you manifested it?
I manifested it.
And the club had, like, all these different rooms.
So it wasn't like we were just, like, in the same space.
I freaking manifested it.
I was literally standing at the bar.
And then I turned to my right.
And he was right there.
And I was like, hello.
Oh.
Hello.
We made out on the malecón, on the wall.
Ooh.
By the water?
Yeah.
Ooh.
That's a Venus and Jupiter in cancer sort of moment.
It was a time.
I'll pull up a picture for you all.
But continue.
Okay.
They like these types of things.
It reminds them that, you know, I've lived a life.
I've lived a life, Laura.
I've lived a life.
Yes.
Gong Ray.
My husband.
My Cuban husband.
He's going to come to America and find me.
Amanda.
Look at Laura's face, y'all.
Wait.
I didn't realize he was also really good looking.
That was the requisite.
I wasn't, like, making out with his character.
It was like, okay, you.
I wasn't making out with his character.
Oh, my God.
I love that this brought us to this side tangent.
Because that's, like, a good visual of what you can manifest for this transit, y'all.
There you go.
It's possible.
You're welcome.